Conor Lamb

Customer Success Engineer

conorlamb11@gmail.com

(720) 362-0822

Thornton, CO

in Linkedin.com/in/conorlamb11

SUMMARY

Technical expert with 6 years of client facing experience and web development experience. Uses a combination of programming expertise and project management skills to assist clients with software implementations focused on complex solutions, integrations, data automations, custom dashboards, and the development of custom utilities and web applications.

Skills

Javascript HTML CSS SQL Angular React Redux Redux Toolkit Node R Studio **REST APIs** Plotly UI / UX Design CPQ Dashboarding Google Visualization Agile NetSuite

EXPERIENCE

Customer Success Engineer

AUG 2023 - PRESENT

Quantive

Remote

- Instructs customer base (including multiple Fortune 500 companies) on all technical features of the platform, including Quantive's Artificial Intelligence (AI) features
- Develops, designs, and provides ongoing maintenance of 300+ insights and dashboards in our application marketplace
- Builds custom integrations to pull data across a software stack into the Quantive Platform
- Automates KPIs and Key Results using SQL queries against the Quantive Database
- Creates custom visualizations ranging from widgets to interactive full page web applications with multiple click paths
- Provides training for junior employees on coding standards and performs code reviews for standardized insights
- Developed and maintains web application that allows Customer Success to easily transfer data across multiple accounts
- Maintains a Node app that uses REST APIs to provide customers with an Excel import/export product feature
- Updates and maintains VSCode Extension allowing for improved custom development within Quantive Platform

Technical Success Manager

AUG 2021 - AUG 2023

Quantive

Remote

- Partnered with Customer Success to lead enterprise customers through technical aspects of software implementations
- . Designed and developed the most visited and highly utilized dashboard across all Quantive clients
- Lead 3 pilot programs for enterprise customers for various land and expand strategies
- Provided technical guidance for pre-sales teams for complex solutions, focused on integrations and automation capabilities within the platform.
- Lead discovery sessions with project executive sponsors for reporting solutions based on desired business outcomes.

Senior CPQ Implementation Consultant / Implementation Consultant

JAN 2018 - AUG 2021

Configure One

Chicago, IL

- Partnered with SMEs at manufacturing companies to build UIs allowing them to more effectively sell complex products
- Built custom scripts to dynamically generate Bills of Materials, and Quote documents based on user inputs
- Leveraged HTML, Javascript, and CSS expertise to customize CPQ interfaces

EDUCATION

Purdue University

Bachelor of Science: Industrial Engineering

West Lafayette, IN

DEC 2017

- Senior Design Project was preparing an "Internet of Things" analysis in a case study for Deloitte
- Designed GUI for a Smart Fridge and integrated SQLQueries to provide information to customers
- Used R Studio functions to scrape data from hockeyreference.com for a statistical analysis on performance indicators

Interests

Basketball Music and Concerts Sitcoms Snowboarding Wakeboarding Purdue Sports